<help title="Rafalh Scripts System" popup="yes">
To show Statistics Panel press F1 (if you have not changed key in settings).
To show User Panel press F2 (if you have not changed key in settings).
Press F5 to show Top Times.
<!--To show command results to everybody use "!" prefix instead of "/" on the command begin.-->
To see full list of commands type "/help".

Most important commands:
/cash [&lt;player&gt;]              - Shows cash and bidlevel for specified player. If no player is specified your cash is shown
/points [&lt;player&gt;]            - Shows points count for specified player. If no player is specified your points are shown
/rank [&lt;player&gt;]              - Shows rank for specified player. If no player is specified your rank is shown
/st [&lt;player&gt;]                - Shows statistics for specified player. If no player is specified your statistics are shown
/besttime [&lt;player&gt;]          - Shows best time of specified player on the current map. If no player is specified your best time is shown
/top &lt;type&gt;                   - Shows top for players currently on server (supported types: lagger, fps_lagger, cash, points, timehere, bidlevel, times)
/gtop &lt;type&gt;                  - Shows global top (supported types: cash, points, timehere, bidlevel)
/votenext &lt;map&gt;               - Start vote for the next map
/check &lt;text&gt;                 - Search for maps with name containing &lt;text&gt;
/maps                         - Shows total maps count
/rating                       - Shows rating of the current map
/rate &lt;1-10&gt;                  - Rates the current map
/race                         - Shows name of the current map
/played                       - Shows how many times current map was played
/players                      - Shows players count
/a                            - Shows alive players
/pm &lt;player&gt; [&lt;message&gt;]      - Starts private chat with player and optionally sends private message
/bet &lt;player&gt; &lt;cash&gt;          - Bet cash on specified player
/unbet                        - Cancels the last bet
/roll                         - Rolls the dice. Your award or punishment depends on the number dice showed
/spin &lt;number&gt; &lt;cash&gt;       - Spins a wheel with numbers from 1 to 65. If the wheel stops on the specified number, you win &lt;cash&gt;*100.
/itemlist                     - Enumerates items in the shop
/buy &lt;item&gt;                   - Buys a shop item
/use &lt;item&gt;                   - Uses a shop item
/setlang &lt;lang code&gt;          - Changes player language
/realcountry [&lt;player&gt;]       - Shows player country read from IP
/givecash &lt;player&gt; &lt;cash&gt;     - Sends your cash to other player
/invitedby &lt;player&gt;           - Sets player who will get an award for inviting you
/commands                     - Shows commands list
</help>